homeportfolio.com 2013-04-01

# About HomePortfolio: Privacy

HomePortfolio believes that protecting your privacy is critical to our mission of customer service excellence. Just as in all of our customer service policies, we are committed to earning your trust through open and honest communication. You have our guarantee that we will not sell or rent your email address for unsolicited marketing. Please look through our privacy policy below for additional details. 

Privacy refers to the ways HomePortfolio collects and uses personal information, as well as to the safeguards we put in place to make sure our practices are fair and adequate. 

As our site acquires new functionality, it might be necessary for us to update our privacy policy periodically to reflect the nature of the new information we might be providing you or asking you to provide us. When that happens, those changes will be posted here. If you have more questions about privacy, or to contact representatives at HomePortfolio, please call 1-617-965-0565.  

### Common Questions about Privacy

****•****  What information do you collect about me?   
**•**  What do you do with my personal information?   
**•**  What happens if I refuse to provide the data you request?   
**•**  What is aggregate data? Do you collect it?   
**•**  Do you use cookies?   
**•**  Do you follow me as I navigate your web site?   
**•**  How can I review and correct my personal data?   
**•**  How do you keep my personal information secure?   
**•**  Whose privacy policies prevail when I link to one of your manufacturers sites?   
**•**  What recourse do I have if there is a problem?

* * *

**What information do you collect about me?** HomePortfolio is guided by the principle of Need to Know. We strive to collect only that information we need to complete your request or to serve you better. We need your email address to send you home design news. We need your zip code to locate retailers near you. And we may ask about your specific home design interests, so that we can better tailor offerings for you. 

Once you have provided basic information for your Home Design Portfolio (name, email address, and zip code), we keep it in your personal account file so you don't have to re- enter it next time. 

  **What do you do with my personal information?** We use your personal information to fulfill your requests and tailor offerings for you. If you tell us that you prefer a certain style of home design products, we may emphasize that style in our presentation to you.

When you become a member of HomePortfolio, we also use your personal information to contact you with home design tips or special members-only offers. Occasionally, we may let you know about other companies whose products or services might be of interest. We may also share your personal information if you link to one of our partner sites, so that our partner site can serve you seamlessly. 

HomePortfolio will also require a screen name and password if you choose to participate in Talk About, HomePortfolio's online community discussion boards. The screen name you select will be used to identify your online presence in Talk About. 

Please be aware that the discussion boards are public venues. If you choose to include personal information in a message or in your author profile, that information will be available to any person viewing or participating in that discussion board. Posting information on public boards may result in unsolicited messages to you and/or the use of such information in a way that is not intended by you. HomePortfolio's ability to delete or modify information which you provide may be limited by technology or its internal procedures/policies and as such HomePortfolio may not be able to mitigate the consequences of your posting such information in a public forum. 

In addition, HomePortfolio may occasionally use portions of a discussion in reference to Talk About for publications and promotions. See Terms of Use. 

Your HomePortfolio registration will pre-register you with our Portfolio Partner sites. Learn about your Home Design Portfolio and how to use it at other sites. Portfolio Partners are clients whose Web sites are powered by HomePortfolio.

The Personal HomeStyle newsletter is jointly administered by HomePortfolio and Better Homes and Gardens.com (BHG.com). If you choose to subscribe to this newsletter, the registration information you provide is subject to joint use by both HomePortfolio and BHG.com. 

In any case where your personal information is shared outside of HomePortfolio, our goal is to have business partners adhere to the same rigorous privacy practices that we do.

As HomePortfolio develops its business, it might sell or buy assets. In such transactions, user information may be one of the transferred business assets. In the event that HomePortfolio Inc. or substantially all of its assets are acquired or merged with another entity, user information is likely to be one of the transferred assets. 

  **What happens if I refuse to provide the data you request?** We clearly mark each request for data with "required" or "optional." "Required" data is necessary to process your request.

"Optional" data lets us know more about you (tastes and preferences for example) so that we can serve you better. Just like your favorite salesperson at your neighborhood store, we want to understand your likes and dislikes so that we can provide tailored services. 

  **What is aggregate data? Do you collect it?** The term "aggregate data" refers to trend information, such as how many people looked at kitchen fixtures yesterday or how many HomePortfolio customers live in urban areas. Aggregate data includes no personally identifiable information. All individual data is anonymous only. We do collect aggregate data and we use it to fine-tune our site design and our offerings to you. In addition, we may share aggregate data with our partner sites so that they too can fine-tune their offerings. 

  **Do you use cookies?** HomePortfolio does use cookies to identify our registered users. This allows us to recognize you when you enter our site, without asking you to log in every time. A cookie is simply a text file on your hard drive, containing a unique string of characters. The HomePortfolio server recognizes your unique string of characters when you visit our site, and is then able to associate your computer with your personal data file on our host computer. That's why we can greet you by name when you visit us again, for example. 

If you choose not to use cookies, you can set your browser to refuse them. In that case, we will have to ask you to log in every time you make use of personalized features such as your Portfolio or Retailer Locator. 

Sometimes we contract with an outside agency to serve banner ads for HomePortfolio. People who click through the ads to visit HomePortfolio may receive cookies. In this case, the cookies are used only to gather aggregate data on advertising effectiveness. 

  **Do you follow me as I navigate your Web site?** Yes, HomePortfolio uses a number called a "session ID" to follow you as you navigate from page to page in our web site. This is the long number you sometimes see at the end of a URL in your browser. The session ID is randomly generated each time you visit us, and contains no personal information about you at all. It also lets us know that the same person who looked at mirrors also wants to see lighting fixtures. 

**How can I review and correct my personal data?** Currently, you can review and correct the information you entered when you originally created your Portfolio, including name, email address, and zip code. Simply enter your Portfolio, and click on the link titled Edit My Account Information.   

  **How do you keep my personal information secure?** HomePortfolio takes many steps to make sure your information is safe on our site. Our mission is to make your 

experience as hassle-free and secure as possible. 

HomePortfolio guarantees the security of your data. If your personal information stored on HomePortfolio is ever used to make an unauthorized purchase, we will refund the portion not covered by your credit card agreement. Under the Fair Credit Billing Act, your bank cannot hold you liable for more than $50.00 of fraudulent charges. If your bank does hold you liable for any of this $50.00, HomePortfolio will cover the entire liability for you, up to the full $50.00. We will cover this liability only if the unauthorized use of your credit card resulted through no fault of your own from purchases made at HomePortfolio while using the secure server. In the unlikely event this happens, you must also notify your credit card provider. 

Rest assured, in the entire history of our site, we have never experienced an unauthorized purchase. Please refer to the Security section for more details on how we keep your information safe once we have collected it. 

  **Whose privacy policies prevail when I link to another site from HomePortfolio?** HomePortfolio's privacy policies apply only to our site. Once you link to another site, their privacy practices prevail. HomePortfolio's goal is to partner only with other businesses that adhere to the same rigorous privacy practices that we do. However, we cannot be responsible for the business practices of other companies. 

  **What recourse do I have if there is a problem?** Our mission is to make your experience as safe and rewarding as possible. If you believe there is a problem, please contact us by phone at 1-617-965-0565. We will make every effort to make things right.
